[
  {
    "id":"01",
    "polishQuestion": "płakać",
    "englishAnswers": [ "cry", "weep" ]
  }, {
    "id":"02",
    "polishQuestion": "wrzeszczeć",
    "englishAnswers": [ "yell", "shout", "cry", "scream" ]
  }, {
    "id":"03",
    "polishQuestion": "tańczyć",
    "englishAnswers": [ "dance", "boogie" ]
  }, {
    "id":"04",
    "polishQuestion": "biegać",
    "englishAnswers": [ "run", "bustle" ]
  }, {
    "id":"05",
    "polishQuestion": "jeździć",
    "englishAnswers": [ "drive", "ride", "travel" ]
  }, {
    "id":"06",
    "polishQuestion": "samochód",
    "englishAnswers": [ "car", "automobile" ]
  }, {
    "id":"07",
    "polishQuestion": "samolot",
    "englishAnswers": [ "airplane", "plane", "aeroplane", "aircraft" ]
  }, {
    "id":"08",
    "polishQuestion": "jacht",
    "englishAnswers": [ "yacht" ]
  }, {
    "id":"09",
    "polishQuestion": "kuchnia",
    "englishAnswers": [ "kitchen", "cooker", "cookery", "cuisine" ]
  }, {
    "id":"10",
    "polishQuestion": "telefon",
    "englishAnswers": [ "telephone", "phone", "call" ]
  }
]
